Filming music videos, recording variety shows, and interviewing for magazines.
Looks like the elected members were living the dream again today.
The election single goes on sale soon too.
In contrast, we've been practicing on our own the whole time.
Jerry's way ahead of us now.
The chosen and the unchosen.
Well, there's nothing we can do.
Jerry's good at singing.
She's really cute when she's got curves in all the right places.
Take all that into account.
It's no wonder someone like me wasn't elected.
Aw, don't be so hurt on yourself.
Yeah, I've got curves and I wasn't elected.
Don't feel bad about that.
Right.
How long are you going to cry about this?
We can't afford to dwell on the general elections forever.
We've got a concert.
Back to work, ladies.
We'll see you in the next episode.
We'll see you next time.
Bye.
心折れそうな 長い桜の前 未来があるなら 背を向けられない
友よ覚えているかい あの日誓い合ったこの場所 季節の花が咲く
主なきその声聞こえるよ太陽がほら少しずつあたりのその闇を剥がしてくれるだろう
主なきさあこの時に僕たちはそう歩き出そう
誰もみんな弱い生き物さ 相投げたい 探しながら先へ進む
This planet has a total entertainment bank, Baltistar.
A civil war between anti-government forces seeking to overthrow the military regime and the DES has been raging on for a while now.
This is going to be a tough one.
This is our first attack concert since the general elections, so it's going to be performed by the elected members.
Who knew the elected member's first concert would be an attack concert? Way to start off with a bang.
I'm ready to go. How wonderful.
The army will try to prevent us from raising anti-government morale.
Expect a fight down there.
To that end, we'll be expanding the support team significantly.
Kanada and the 76th generation trainees will pilot LAS alongside the Woda mobile forces and protect the Kanada.
Right!
As for the 77th generation trainees, you'll also have an important job to carry out.
Huh?
Uh-huh!
77th generation trainees have successfully infiltrated.
It's just as Woda's intel described.
We found young boys being transported for forced labor.
Our target, Vegastar, is a military base constructed by the DGTO to maintain order on Baltistar.
But we've received information that for some reason, high-ranking government officials and
important civilian businessmen and scholars have been coming and going.
It's your job to investigate their activities.
From this point on, all our communications will be encrypted.
I pray for the success of your mission.
It's finally time.
Infiltration mission.
I'm feeling nervous.
Do you think these disguises will really work?
Don't worry about it.
Just think of this as a chance to put all that acting training to good use.
We will succeed, no matter what dangers await us.
Come on, Ben, let me hear your battle cries.
Hold on.
If they catch us, we'll be interrogated for sure.
Great.
We've checked all their IDs.
Good.
Huh.
Starting today, you will all be handling routine tasks for the supply divisions.
If you want to return to your home soon, you better work like your life depends on it.
Yes, sir.
Private Higashino.
Uh, yes, sir.
I want you to look after these kids for me.
Show them how we do things.
Uh, uh...
Aye, aye, sir!
Thierry!
What's wrong?
You're looking gloomy.
The concert's starting soon.
Yuko-san.
You're worried about the infiltration team.
Is that it?
No way.
I trust them to do their job like I trust myself to do mine.
That's the spirit.
Keep up that attitude.
Come on, boys.
Put your backs into it.
Ugh.
My hips.
If you don't work harder, you'll never finish.
Yes, sir.
There.
That's a ton of fun.
That's a ton of laundry, right, bro?
Right, man.
All right.
Here's another batch.
Work faster or you'll never finish.
Uh, thanks, dude.
Seriously, you can't even handle this much of a load?
Oops.
Like that.
Oh.
I can't take it, man.
What a worthless bunch of kids.
Until you finish your work, don't expect to see dinner.
Crap.
Why'd Lieutenant Monkey have to assign me to look after these kids?
I hate kids!
Yeah, well, the feeling's mutual, bub.
I didn't think it would be this tough.
Huh?
Hey, guys.
Where's Makoto?
Huh?
She was here a moment ago.
Scrub, scrub, scrub, scrub, scrub, scrub, scrub, scrub.
Makoto?
What's going on?
You're unusually fired up.
Do you enjoy cleaning toilets?
I'll clean toilets or whatever else you want.
After all, I wasn't chosen.
Huh.
Ugh.
Girls.
Oh.
We just received an encrypted message from Katayusha to begin our mission.
Dude.
Zero-zero spotted on Baltistar.
I repeat.
Interceptors launch.
Stop all entertainment immediately.
Looks like it started.
Mm.
OK.
Let's split into units and carry out the plan.
Got it.
Come on, everyone.
Let's go, Knicks.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Hey, guys.
I want you.
I need you.
I love you.
We need love and shine.
They're here! All units dispersed!
Roger!
I won't let you interrupt the elected member's first concert!
Hit me with your best shot!
Huh?
Where are we?
It seems to be the armory.
What?
All of this?
Whoa!
Heavy rotation?
That's heavy rotation, alright?
But why would a Zero Zero song be playing inside a TES base?
Maybe it's the concert. They could be monitoring.
Let's check it out!
You're kidding!
Can you crack it?
Hey, what's that?
Huh?
Nice, Kodo!
Hey, it's getting louder!
It's the main event, folks!
And the stage is set!
VoltaStar!
A planet with a total entertainment fan!
How will the forces of military-based Vegastar battle against Zero Zero?
What?
Zodiac unmanned combat machines!
The pride of the DES!
The DES elite forces are raring to go!
Now, I ask you, ladies and gentlemen,
how long will Zero Zero be able to continue performing?
10,000 on 5 minutes!
50,000 on 10 minutes!
100,000 on 20 minutes!
Is that the Gorilla concert going on right now?
What does she mean?
How long can they keep performing?
This place is a casino!
There's no mistake!
They're betting money on Zero Zero's concert!
You're kidding!
That's what's happening to our concerts?
That must mean...
It's an illegal underground casino!
This is the planet's secret?
Unforgivable!
They pretend to ban entertainment while raking in cash behind the scenes?
Yuka, we need to get in for a closer look!
Ah!
Oh!
Intruders in the casino?
Who are they?
Zero Zero members!
Zero Zero here?
Get them!
But those are...
You're surrounded!
Give up and come quietly!
In your dreams, pal!
We never listen to hypocritical DES garbage like you!
Hmph!
Ah!
Sorry, Lieutenant!
Zero Zero members have infiltrated the base!
Find and capture them immediately!
What?
Do you think they found Nagisa and the others?
I hope they're okay!
Ah!
Hello!
Can you hear me?
Yuka?
Oh, good!
You're all right!
This place stinks!
Encrypt your message!
We don't have time for that!
Listen!
An illegal casino?
Yes!
They've been betting on fights between DES and Zero Zero!
So the DGTO is making huge profits supporting underground entertainment!
I can't believe they've managed to keep it hidden from us for so long!
But it all makes sense now!
The DGTO attacks have been unnaturally weak lately!
They must have done it to promote their gambling!
Zero Zero has stolen DGTO's greatest secrets and they are attempting to escape!
Fire!
Shadow!
We're in your control room, knocking out your dudes!
Great job. Now let's look for an escape route.
The elected members in Kaneda-san are risking their lives down on the planet.
Now that I know their efforts are being disrespected like this,
there's no way we could just run away!
We have to do something about it!
Orine?
I found something.
It looks like there's a large nuclear reactor in the center of this asteroid.
If we can stop it, we may be able to interrupt the power supply and cause massive power outage.
That should put a stop to their gambling.
A power outage?
That would shut down all the cameras and security systems, too!
I'm all for it!
It's reckless, but it's something Zero-Zero would do!
Yeah, let's do it!
Things are starting to get wild, ladies and gentlemen!
Zero-Zero agents are loose in this base and seem to be planning to shut down the reactor!
The action's heating up! Let the surprise bedding begin!
Will Zero-Zero be able to reach the reactor and escape this facility?
Or will the D.E.S. stop them and take them prisoner?
You did it with me! Place your best!
Leave us!
We need to find a way to direct the D.E.S.'s attention away from the reactor.
Uh, let's see! Would a fainting plan work?
What's that would fainting do? We need a faint!
Isn't that what I said?
Well...
Couldn't we use this?
Oh!
I came in.
We have a boss who's inside and inside
What...
Thanks for the lift!
Come on! Wipe that concern from your face!
You don't want to worry your fans, do you?
Come on! Let's give them a smile!
You're the king!
You can do it!
It's crawling with DES soldiers.
This is as close as we're getting.
Huh?
We've arrived at the reactor. Stay on target.
Where's the brakes at?
There we go!
Awesome! The others made it!
This is our chance! Let's go!
Okay!
Wait!
Amazing!
And yet I'm just sitting here.
There it is!
Makochi's famous knees up face down pose!
Huh?
Seeing Makochi's sad face in person is like a dream come true!
Higashino-san?
That's Private Higashino to you!
Why'd you have to come to such a dangerous place?
Something could happen to you!
What's going on?
I'm DES Soldier and Secret Zero Zero Fan Private Higashino!
Yeah, baby! Do me a solid and keep that quiet!
Anyway, everyone else is fighting, but what are you doing Makochi?
Uh...
Even if I go, there's nothing I can do to help them.
I'm not any good as an idol.
I'm not any good on missions.
When you get right down to it, I'm not good at anything.
You really are hopeless, aren't you?
As another person from Naniwastar, I'm embarrassed for you!
Huh?
Your jokes are lame and you got no backbone.
It's so pathetic, I can't watch!
You don't have to put it like that!
But you know what?
I always want to support cowards like you, Makochi.
I even voted for you in the general elections!
You voted for me?
Oh, yeah! Four times, actually!
I put all my meager wages into it!
Besides, it ain't about numbers!
It's about heart and love, isn't it?
Uh, right!
But, uh, why would you vote for a coward like me?
I guess you grew on me.
I did?
A bird who can't fly isn't very cool and can't do anything.
But you never tried to hide the fact that you couldn't fly.
You just accepted it!
Watching you fail warms my own weak heart.
I mean, if someone brave enough to join AKB can still be a coward,
there's no reason to beat myself up for my own weaknesses.
Oddly, it makes me feel less alone.
Hikashima-san!
They're fighting hard.
If you turn off the emergency control lever directly underneath here,
you could stop the reactor.
Hikashima-san?
Huh?
Makono!
What is she doing over there?
That's the control lever?
Yes!
If you can push down the middle one!
Then the power will go out!
You can't do this!
It's impossible!
This is more dangerous than bungee jumping!
I have nothing to lose!
Huh?
You're right.
I can't fly like everyone else.
And most days, I can't even manage to be positive.
Ugh!
I'm only myself!
Ah!
Wow!
Oh, no! She missed it!
Oh, no!
She did it! Yes!
Oh, crap! That's the win, ladies! Way to go, Buddha!
From now on, you'll be the great Buddha! Amazing! Great job!
Wow! This is certainly an unexpected outcome! Zero-Zero's plan managed to succeed!
Hey! There's earlock!
Higashino-san?
The power's out, remember? That means I gotta close it manually!
This is goodbye, Makochi!
Been a real honor! I'll be rooting for ya!
Thank you very much!
We are handling the leaked information about the casino by ordering all regions to keep quiet.
However, now that Zero-Zero has the information, it's very possible it may be exposed as a scandal.
No matter. Compared to the value of the data we acquired, it is a small risk.
Rising spirits and shining Carrara, huh?
No matter.
Sure, butThis depends on where we ao waste the damage you are.
Just a thousand years left...
Which will happen despite concerninger perfection...
Deskis to help finding out aAyuda-zero's plan.
My dream is within the ground
But afelice time with a希望
will, too, go into the next day
When we met in some event
wishing for it is still there
onlylegt
not all times
花は咲くのだろう
この涙を君に捧ぐ
もっと君が輝くなら
ずっと見守ってた深奥の空から
今僕は雨になろう
君に捧ぐ こんな僕にできることは
君の虚しさを少しでも癒すこと
さあ僕は雨になろう
ず誰か悔しが
あれそう
Thank you.